Oh!
Pakkan!
Bon appétit!
Bombinos
Bombinos.
What do we do? I'm going to get burned.
Burn, burn, burn!
Wow!
Let's eat.
You want to take a picture?
Take a picture after we open it.
Open first.
I'll open it.
What? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh!
Pow!
Wow!
Can you see it?
It's so hot!
It's so gooey!
It's boiling!
It's so hot!
It looks so good!
That's great!
Looks so good!
Shall we serve?
Let's sleigh.
Wow! You're so crumbly!
Did you put the onigiku in here?
Yes!
Under the strawberries.
It's so good!
You want some?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Do you have any onigiku?
Oh, no.
I don't see anything. It's melting.
Does meat melt? No, it's melting.
Is it stuck? Down there.
What do you mean? It's stuck.
Did you put it in there? We ate it together, didn't we?
Oh, my God!
You got it?
Really? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, look, look, look.
What? Is it down there?
No, it's not down there. If it was, I'd be using it right now.
Oh, I found one.
One for now.
It's hot down there.
It's hot.
Thanks.
Thank you.
I'm the only one who's big. I'm the only one who eats like a pig.
I want to start a fire.
Look at that. It's getting low.
I guess it's time.
Oh, I'm gonna eat so much.Oh, I eat so much!
preserve10.2
First of all, the box is cute!
It's going to be small.
Now, why don't you put some rice in the box?
Oh, and rice...
Let's put rice in it.
You want to put it in?
You can put it in.
Oh, yeah.
Did you see another one?
You want to put it all in?
Oh, there it is, rice.
Rice.
That's rice, you didn't use it.
It's gonna go bang, isn't it?
Boom.
It's hot, right? Are you okay?
Let's do it.
Here we go.
Oh!
It's really sticking.
You got it?
I got it!
It's good, it's good, it's good.
I think it's gonna crack.
Ahhh...
Ohhhhh...
Oh, no.
It's hot, isn't it? My hand.
Hot, isn't it?
Wow, this is gonna be fun.
Hey.
Can we keep going?
Yeah, thanks.
I mean, this is good, right? Is it good?
You know, this itself...
Can I eat your foot?
Yeah, sure.
Are they still warm?
Are you okay?
I'm good!
I'll eat it!
Is it good?
I don't know, do you?
Mmm!
Mmm! Mmm!
That's good!
Mmm. - Yeah.
Yum.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's like a snack.
It's so good!
It's delicious!
It's done!
I knew this was important.
Yeah, it's really important!Hey, it's very important!
If you don't have this, it's going to fly away.
I think I put it in all the meat.
You want to come in?
Yeah, sure.
I'm looking forward to dinner.
Hey!
Bombinos? It's called Bombinos.
Bombinos.
It's a good fit.
It's nice.
I'm going to sing "Bombinos.
Bombinos.
Is it good? Delicious!
I love tomato casserole.
Calami, are you okay with the cold?
It's cold.
I can't pull it aside anymore. It's so cold today.
Two days never come.
You're so cute!
You two are so cute!
You look like campers!
I always wanted to be a camper!
I want to be a camper, even if it's just to look like one.
Earlier, Piyo and I left for a while, right?
And when we came back, Kanami said something to me like
Like a good camper.
Like a girl who camps solo.
She looked like a girl who camps by herself!
She had a nice silhouette!
Oh, that's nice!
Next time
And this is a great hanpen!
It's so thick!
It's got cheese in it.
It's like it's not a hampen at all.
Marshmallow
Why is it different?
Here you go.
Yay!
I hope they turn out good.
What do you do when you get a burnt round?
All four.
But there's a net here.
The fire's on this side.
Oh, yeah.
This side is really hot.
Oh, are you okay?
The handle's on.
Looks delicious.
Oh, wow.
A little more on this side.
That's a great drawing.
So cute!
It's kind of checkered.
He's not here, so I'm gonna eat him.
Oh, my God! Look at his face!
Here he comes.
He's messing with Pugh right now.
He's coming for my throat.The one that comes down your throat.
I was just messing with Karami.
It's like a hamburger.
Oh no, wait, it's a bump, it's a bump!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Aaahhh...
Oh no!
Uh-oh.
But...
If I just shave off a little bit here and there, it'll be fine.
I can eat it, I can eat it
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
This is tough.
What I said came true.
I see.
Oh, I took it.
But it looks delicious.
Don't burn it.
Oh, shake?
Oh, okay.
I got it.
Wait, it's shrinking.
It's shrinking, guys.
Oh, no, no, no.
Is this one okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
Oh, my God, it shrunk.
It's hot, I know.
It's delicious.
Oh, the way to go.
Oh, sounds great.
Oh, it looks so good!
The cheese is growing.
Yum.
Yum! Yum!
Yum. - Yum.
Yum.
Yum. Yum.
Oh, yummy yummy!
And it doesn't taste burnt.
Hey, it's burnt, but it doesn't taste burnt.
Oh, that's good!
Yummy!
More camp food!
Add campaign!
Yummy!
Fireworks!
NO
I got a no
The voice in my mind said
no.
no
No. Fun.
Great.
Come on, the fire is almost out.Come. The fire is almost out.
Canamins and apioca
Come again.
And again.
Ha-ha-ha.
Also...
Thank you.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Look!
Wait a minute, please.
Wait a minute!
Look! I brought you something.
Thank you.
I've got to get it in.
I'll get it in. I'll get it in.
Can you hold this pan for a second?
Is it hot?
Are you okay?
Pombinos.
Pombinos?
What's right?
Pombinos.
It's nice fishing with Mt. Fuji.
It's cool.
I can take a picture.
Pombinos
By the way, there are people around.
By the way.
I don't like it.
It looks like it's on fire.
What do you think?
Oh! Jokin!
Jokin?
Jokin!
Peo raised you, didn't he?
Yes, he did.
Thank you for raising me like this.
Thank you.
I'll save some of this for you.
Bombinos, right? You want some milk?
Let's do it.
Oh, there it is! Milk and cheese.
Put the cheese in there first.
Oh, bon vinos.
Are we done? Still here?
For now. But, you know, seasoning.
Do you have soy sauce? We have soy sauce.
Really? Yeah, it's in the soy sauce case.
It's delicious.
Hello.
Today.
Neo and I came to Dog Rye.
They're letting Huell in, too.
Neo.
It's been a long trip.That was a long trip.
I heard they have some kind of food.
This place looks like a dock run.
Let's go in.
Covered dock run.
No weight limit.
I'm off!
There's a lot of friends here.
Let's get the leash.
Hello, there.
Hello. - Hello.
Mr. Balchies?
I'm Balchies.
You look like a goat over here.
He's cute.
His face is like a Balchies.
So cute!
Hello.
How old is he?
Maybe a year and a half.
My son is eight.
People mistake me for a baby all the time.
Wait. Sit.
Sit, sit, wait.
Wait for me.
No? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you very much for your help.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no, no, no, you scared me.
It's a bug.
It's delicious.
Bugs.
Good night.
(5) I'm going home.
(6) Good friends
Good friends, good friends
Good night, good night, good night
Good night.
I just went to the 1st dog line
Rio-kun, you got along well with us, a lot!
Rio is so happy already!
I wonder what this is.
It's for small dogs under 8 kilograms.
Rio weighs 3 kilograms.
He can totally fit in there.
Rio is under 8 kg, so he can go in.
Rio is under 8 kilograms, so he's in.
Mick, are you tired?
Can't you run anymore?
Come on!
Are you tired?
Do you want some water?
We're at the next other dog run.
He's the biggest one.
It's an uber.
I'm pretty sure that's not what you smell.I'm pretty sure that's not what you smell.
Okay?
Right?
Play with it.
Okay?
Come here, come here, come here.
Come here, come here, come here, come here.
Come here. Come here.
Hey? - Hey. Here.
Here.
Climb up here.
Right?
Don't you want to climb?
No?
I've already soiled my gibbons.
Hito.
I'll shorten them. I'll start shortening them now.
Here... these pants...
Here, I'll take these. They'll be shorts.
They're soiled.
Pheo.
Here, here, here, here.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's great.
Let's try again.
Let's do it again.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
This way, this way
Come on!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come here, come here, come here. Oh, yeah, you're good. Come here, come here, come here.
Come here, boy.
Oh, wow, Len, you did it.
Come here, come here.
Come on.
Go through this hole.
Try it.
Once you can visualize it, it's like this.
Come here! Come here!
My dog is not interested.
It's hot! Look! Beautiful!
Purple, purple, pink and white.
Hot! Hot!
Hot! It's so hot!
Let's take a break!
Let's take a break! I'm going to eat!
It's so hot! It's so hot!
I'm going to bed!
Ta-da!
I bought snacks!
I got snacks!
Now that's a good sound.
Want some?Eating?
I've got a video of me reacting to a group line about my family.
I'm taking a video of you reacting.
That's great.
See you in the next video.
Bye.
My meal, Margherita Tan!
I've had it!
Super nice!
I'll take it!
Good night.
Well, you know, I drove home today.
Well, the first tragedy is that, uh...
I forgot my GoPro, and I was 10 minutes away from home.
But I had to have it.
My sister happened to be at home today and called me.
I asked her to deliver it to my house, and she did it.
Also, I think I got off at the wrong place on the highway.
I'm not good at U-turns.
And it was a tight spot.
My heart was racing, but I made it.
Thank goodness.
Finished the meal!
We finished our meal.
It was delicious.
Next time
We're going to the pool!
The main event of the day.
But I've never been in a pool before.
I don't know if I can get in.
But I bought a ticket.
I'm going.
Listen, Leo, I can't really take pictures of you because you're like a photo booth.
I got a pretty good shot just now.
What? Isn't he cute? Hey, let's go to the pool, okay?
Let's go to the pool.
This way. Oh! It's all yours.
Penkun, I'm going to take a shower.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
You go ahead. Come here.
Are you scared? I'll be fine.
I'm fine. Rather! Rather!
Penquin, I'd rather.
Good night.
Laughing.
LOL!
Laughter.
Good night.
Laughter
LOL!
Folks, apparently Leo doesn't go in the pool.
I mean, this is all Leo's sweaty feet.
Yes, it's sad that I paid the pool fee and he won't go in.
I don't think it's really good to force him in.
I wish he could go in.
I think it would be fun.
But she's scared.
If she's scared, I don't blame her.If you're scared, it can't be helped.
Scary things are scary, aren't they?
Hey, Leo.
Come here!
What?
Mm-hmm.
Excited.
Come on.
Phew!
Yes, sir.
So today I came to the storehouse with Leo. I guess we didn't get to go in the pool. Sorry, Leo.
I'm sorry Leo, I'm sorry you didn't get to go in the pool.
I had a good day today too!
Good button and like button and subscribe to our channel. Bye bye, bye, bye.
Bye-bye, Leo. Bye-bye, Leo.
Bye-bye.